{
    "subject": "resource/South_China_AA",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "resource/Che_Runqiu",
    "human_readable": "South China AA's name is Che Runqiu.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9849859476089478,
            "question": "Is Che Runqiu associated with South China AA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9567541480064392,
            "question": "What is the significance of Che Runqiu's name in relation to South China AA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9213360548019409,
            "question": "What can we learn about the nature of South China AA based on its name association with Che Runqiu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8743705749511719,
            "question": "Are there any historical records or documents that mention Che Runqiu and South China AA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8203595876693726,
            "question": "What is the name of South China AA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.812906801700592,
            "question": "Does South China AA have a known name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7688647508621216,
            "question": "Who is Che Runqiu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6363073587417603,
            "question": "What other names or titles might be used for South China AA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5663353800773621,
            "question": "Could there be multiple individuals named Che Runqiu associated with different organizations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44151943922042847,
            "question": "Are there any other individuals associated with South China AA?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=South China AA's name is Che Runqiu.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4892_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could there be multiple individuals named Che Runqiu associated with different organizations?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4892_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other names or titles might be used for South China AA?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4892_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Che Runqiu?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4892_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4892_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4892_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4892_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4892_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4892_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4892_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4892_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4892_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4892_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4892_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text does mention that \"defender Che Runqiu made a run into the JDT area\" but it doesn't say that his name is South China AA's name.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n`{'output': 'no'}`\n\nThe documents mention \"Runqiu Che\" as a player, but there is no indication that he is associated with the team \"South China AA\". The team mentioned in relation to Runqiu Che is actually called \"Southern Tigers\", and later referred to as just \"Southern\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context does not contain any information related to South China AA or a player named Che Runqiu in that specific context. Therefore, the statement \"South China AA's name is Che Runqiu\" cannot be supported by the given documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}